Oh, my God!
Oh no, no, no!
I would like to interview Akihiro!
What are your charm points?
Here we go!
Seino
Charm point
Hello everyone, I'm Haruka Kuromi from Nogizaka 46.
Let me tell you where I am right now.
Ta-da!
I'm here at the Miyazaki Camp!
I've been told that the players of Samurai Japan are training for the Asian Professional Baseball Championship
Samurai Japan players are training for the Asian Professional Baseball Championship
I'm here to cover it!
Please check out the video on Prime Video's YouTube channel.
I hope you will check out the full story on Prime Video's YouTube channel.
During the video streaming, I'd like to show you the behind-the-scenes of the interview.
Please watch until the end!
I'm off!
Okay, let's go.
I'm going to sneak into the practice with a black body notebook.
I'll also be doing some interviews.
I'm looking forward to it.
I'm a little nervous.
Yes, you are.
I'm looking forward to it.
Yes, I understand.
I'd like to do a lot of interviews today.
From now on, right?
I was wondering if I might be able to interview Akihiro.I was wondering if I might be able to interview Akihiro.
What do you want to ask him?
I have the impression that he is very conscious of left-handed pitchers.
I wanted to know about that.
Also, I heard that you are trying to gain weight.
I'd like to know what kind of training he does on a regular basis.
I'd be very interested to hear what kind of training you do on a regular basis.
On a personal note
He has a big crocodile cushion that he loves to use.
I was wondering if you are bringing it to the camp this time.
I was wondering if you are bringing it to the camp.
I hope to hear about that too!
Please let me know next time.
Thank you very much.
You have a great aura.
Yo!
Spider
Good morning.
Nice to meet you.
I'm Kuroiwa.
I'm Haruka Kuroiwa.
Please check the data.
I'd like to ask you a few questions.
Various questions.
Please answer a lot of questions.
This is Haruka Kuroiwa.
Pleased to meet you.
Akihiro.
Wait a minute, please.
I'm sorry.I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
I'm sweating.
I would like to interview Akihiro.
Nice to meet you, Akihiro!
I heard that you have a big crocodile cushion
I heard that you have a big crocodile cushion in your house.
Can I have my microphone back, please?
Excuse me.
You're 19 years old?
Nineteen.
You know your way around.
Thank you very much.
Thank you very much, Akihiro.
Good luck.
I'm going to the bullpen now, so I can watch the players pitch. What a rare opportunity!
What should I do?
It looks amazing. I know it's amazing, but...
That's all I can think of right now. But that's how excited I am.
I'm looking forward to it.
Isn't it amazing?
I'm sure Akovs will be checking out the way you hit the ground after you lift your last leg.
After he lifts his leg at the end.
Nemoto's change-up.
Miyagi for his change-up.
So that's something to look out for, too.
Wow!
That was amazing!It was amazing!
I was surprised at the report, too, because it was my first time to experience it.
But more than that, the bullpen was so powerful!
I should have been able to cover the event, but
But I started watching as a fan.
I thought I was in trouble halfway through.
Reporting is more difficult than I thought.
I have to put into words what was happening on the spot.
It's really difficult to put into words what happened on the spot.
I wondered what kind of practice they were doing.
But now I can see it here.
I was able to learn a lot by seeing them in person.
I was able to learn a lot about them by seeing them in person.
It's difficult to report, but I learned a lot.
I learned a lot.
I'm going to interview Mr. Hayakawa on short notice.
Mr. Hayakawa is one of my seniors
I would like to ask him about various aspects of pitching
I want to hear about various aspects of his pitching.
I'll be there.
He was born in the same year that his family made their first appearance at Koshien.
I know him well.
I heard you have a dog.
What are some of his charms?
Charm point.
Thank you very much.
You have a great face.
Thank you very much. Thank you.
Good luck.
Thank you very much.
I've been doing some research, going through the Internet, looking at videos of you pitching.
And read what the coaches and managers are saying in camp.
And then I actually go to the official channel of the team, the Save Lions, for example.
There's a lot of behind-the-scenes footage of Sato.
I watch them and analyze the information there.
I'd like to have dinner now.
There's a food stall, so I bought what I wanted to eat there.
Beef skewers made from Miyazaki Prefecture's black beef.
Isn't this amazing?
Bon appétit!
Mmmm! It's so tender and grilled over charcoal? It's so tender and grilled over charcoal?
It's delicious!
There are also rice balls rolled with meat and chicken nanban!
I heard that Miyazaki is famous for its chicken nanban.
Chicken Nanban and Yakitori!
Tei alimentos
champion
Now, I think I'm going to Tomisaka main place.
This is Haruka Kuromi's question-and-answer session.
I would like to talk to Kadowaki now.
Pleased to meet you.
It didn't seem like it was much of a first year for you.
If I were probably a first-year baseball player
I would have been too busy doing what was in front of me to play baseball.
I couldn't think of managing myself like that.
To manage myself wellTo keep yourself in check.
I carry all kinds of things with me.
I think it's really great that you have a lot of awareness
I think it's a wonderful thing to be able to learn directly from seniors and directors.
I also think it's great that you can learn directly from your seniors and supervisors.
I also felt that they have really good communication skills, being able to learn directly from their seniors and supervisors.
I wish I had such a good first year.
Looking back now
I want to look at things now.
There are so many things.
Amazing.
Today.
I'd like to buy souvenirs for the members of the baseball team
What do you think?
T-shirts
And towels.
Towels like these.
There are so many kinds of towels!
Look at this cover!
Ta-da!
Isn't it cute?
What should I choose?
Oh, that one, right?
It's the Samurai Japan version of the WBC one I have.
I'll buy this one.
I bought this.
I'm buying this!
Oh, no, no, no!
I'm going to interview Maki now.I'm going to interview Maki now.
I'd like to get to the interview before Maki gets on Mushroom.
Thank you for watching.
We're going to hear about Maki's experience in the WBC and this kind of thing.
And finally, I'm sure you all know
I'm sure you all know that many of you carry a towel with you at live concerts.
I'd like to ask you to do that with me.
I wonder if it's possible.
Now, I would like to ask Maki a question.
Maki, please say hello.
Pleased to meet you.
Do your teammates ask you about your valuable experience in the WBC?
Also, do you talk with your teammates?
When the team becomes united.
I hope I can show them that.
Thank you very much.
There's one last thing I'd like to do.
Can I ask you for a favor?
I'd like to ask you to face the camera.
Destasha.
May I?
Yes, please.
Here we go.
Ready.
Destasha.
Thank you very much.
You're right.
I've often seen them getting excited on the bench or something.
I wondered what it was like.I wondered what it would be like.
But when I talked to him, he's very kind and cheerful.
And he is cheerful, but I felt again that he has a serious and sincere attitude toward baseball.
I felt again that you have a serious and sincere attitude toward baseball, and I was a little nervous.
I was also a little nervous.
And after all, I was most happy to be able to perform.
I was most happy to be able to perform.
I was very happy to be able to face the camera during the broadcast.
Well, the interview is over!
It was really hectic, we were in the middle of having dinner when we decided to go.
There was a lot of running.
It was really just a moment.
We had a great time.
Thank you very much.
I hope that the activities of the Norisaka Baseball Club will expand again.
I hope that the activities of the Norisaka Baseball Club will expand again and that I will be able to participate in many more events in the future.
Thank you very much for the valuable experience today!
Please subscribe to our channel and give us a high rating!
I'll be waiting for you.
See you soon!